<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Planti</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="Welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="st">Strawberries are cultivated worldwide.This fruit is widely appreciated for its characteristic: \nAroma,   Bright red color,   Juicy texture,  Sweetness. It is consumed in large quantities, either fresh or in such prepared foods as\n Jam, Juice, Pies, Ice Cream, Milkshakes, Chocolates etc.\n\n 1 cup of sliced, fresh strawberries, or 166 grams(g), contains nutrients:\n✓   Calories:   53 Calories\n✓   Crotein:   1.11 g\n✓    Carbohydrates:   12.7 g\n✓   Cietary fiber:   3.30 g\n✓   Calcium:   27 Milligrams (mg)\n✓    Iron:   0.68 mg\n✓    Magnesium:   22 mg\n✓    Phosphorus:   40 mg\n✓    Potassium:   254 mg\n✓    Vitamin C:   97.60 mg\n✓    Folate:   40 Micrograms\n✓    Vitamin A:     20 International units     "</string>
    <string name="gr"> Grapes are the most common fruit and are also the oldest cultivated plant throughout the world.Grapes are about 80 percent water. Grapes also add fiber to the diet.\nGrapes come in three basic colors:\ngreen (sometimes called white), red and blue-black. Red grapes are rich in quercetin.\nNutritional Facts serving size 1(1/2) cups (138g/14.9oz)\n✓  Calories : 90\n✓  Calories from Fat : 10\n✓  Total Fat : 0g\n✓  Sodium 0mg : 0%\n✓  Potassium 270mg : 8%\n✓  Total Carbohydrate(24g) : 8%\n✓  Dietary Fiber(1g) : 2%\n✓  Sugars : 23g\n✓  Protein : 1g\n✓  Vitamin-A : 2%\n✓  Vitamin-C : 25%\n✓  Calcium : 2%\n✓  Iron : 2%     "</string>
    <string name="ch">Cherry trees generally start bearing fruit in their fourth year; dwarf trees bear fruit a year earlier. One mature, standard-size tart or sweet cherry tree will produce 30 to 50 quarts of cherries each year; a dwarf tree, about 10 to 15 quarts.\nCherries are a colorful summer staple featured in Pies, Jams, or enjoyed on their own as a light snack.\nCherries are particularly lovely fruit trees the blossoms are beautiful (the reason for cherry blossom festivals all over the world each year),\n the fruit is tasty, and the trees are quite easy to grow, with just a little care and knowledge.\n\n 1 cup of fresh cherries contains:\n\n✓   Calories  :  95\n✓   Protein  :  1.6 grams (g)\n✓   Fat  :  0.3 g\n✓   Carbohydrate  :  24 g\n✓   Fiber  :  3.2 g (making them a good source)\n✓   Sugars  :  19.2 g\n✓   Calcium  :  20 milligrams (mg)\n✓   Iron  :  0.5 mg\n✓   Magnesium  :  17 mg\n✓   Potassium  :  333 mg\n✓   Vitamin-C  :  10.5 mg (making them a </string>
    <string name="le">The lemon is a species of small evergreen trees in the flowering plant family Rutaceae, native to Asia, primarily Northeast India (Assam), Northern Myanmar or China.\nLemons are an excellent source of vitamin C and flavonoids, which are antioxidants.\nAntioxidants help remove free radicals that can damage cells from the body.\nThese nutrients can help preventTrusted Source diseases and boost health and wellbeing.\n\nOne lemon weighing 58 grams (g) containsTrusted Source:\n\n✓  Energy: 16.8 calories (kcal)\n✓  Carbohydrates: 5.41 g, of which 1.45 g are sugars\n✓  Calcium 15.1 milligrams (mg)\n✓  Iron  : 0.35 mg\n✓  Magnesium  : 4.6 mg\n✓  Phosphorus  : 9.3 mg\n✓  Potassium  : 80 mg\n✓  Selenium  :  0.2 micrograms (mcg)\n✓  Vitamin-C  : 30.7 mg\n✓  Folate  : 6.4 mcg\n✓  Choline  : 3.0 mg\n✓  Vitamin-A  : 0.6 mcg\n✓  Lutein + Zeaxanthin : 6.4 mcg</string>
    <string name="mu">Mulberry is used for its fruit, as a delicious vegetable, for medicinal purposes, landscaping and the leaves and stems are used as animal fodder.\nMulberry, in its young shrub stage, is excellent forage for ruminant animals such as sheep and goats and monogastrics such as pigs. The leaves and stems are delicious for animals and very digestible.\n\nNutritional Content of Mulberry:\n\n✓  Crude Protein    :    15-20% \n✓  Minerals    :     25% \n✓   Dry Matter    :     25-30% \n✓   Digestibility     :    70-90% \n✓   Palatability     :     High    </string>
    <string name="po">Potato is the fourth mjor food crop after RICE, WHEAT and MAIZE in the world. It produces high dry matter, balanced protein and high calories.\nPotato tubes contain Vitamin-C and Vitamin-B.It provides carbohydrates,minerals and fibre.The protein is as comparable to that of milk and egg.
    </string>
    <string name="stc">\n ✓    Keep strawberry beds mulched to reduce water needs and weed invasion. Any type of mulch—from black plastic to pine straw to shredded leaves—will keep the soil moist and the plants clean. Read more about mulching.
\n\n ✓    Be diligent about weeding. Weed by hand, especially in the first months after planting.
\n\n ✓    Moisture is incredibly important to strawberries due to their shallow roots. Water adequately, about one inch per square foot per week. Strawberry plants need a lot of water when the runners and flowers are developing and again in the late summer, when the plants are fully mature and gearing up for winter dormancy.
\n\n ✓    Fertilize with all-purpose granules for strong growth. In warm weather, berries ripen about 30 days after blossoms are fertilized.
\n\n ✓    In the first year, pick off blossoms to discourage strawberry plants from fruiting. If not allowed to bear fruit, they will spend their food reserves on developing healthy roots instead, which is a good thing. The yields will be much greater in the second year.
\n\n ✓    Eliminate runner plants as needed. First and second generations produce higher yields. Try to keep daughter plants spaced about 10 inches apart.
\n\n ✓    Row covers are a good option for protecting blossoms and fruit from birds</string>
    <string name="std">\n ✓    Provide adequate space for sprawling. Set plants out 18 inches (1-1/2 feet) apart to leave room for runners and leave 4 feet between rows. Strawberries are sprawling plants. Seedlings will send out runners, which in turn will send out their own runners.
\n\n ✓    Make planting holes deep and wide enough to accommodate the entire root system without bending it. However, don’t plant too deep! The roots should be covered, but the crown should be right at the soil surface. It is very important that you do NOT bury the crown (central growing bud) of the plant or it could rot. The leaves, flowers, and fruit must be exposed to light and fresh air.
\n\n ✓    To settle their roots into the soil, water plants well at the time of planting.
\n\n ✓    It is also possible to grow strawberries from last years runners.</string>
    <string name="lo">Breast cancer is a disease in which cells in the breast grow out of control. Breast cancer can begin in different parts of the breast and spread outside the breast through blood vessels and lymph vessels.Breast cancer is second leading cancer death in women.\nThe disease occurs almost entirely in <b>Women</b>,but <b>Men</b> can get it, too   </string>
    <string name="st"><b> Breast cancer stage is from 0 to 4.</b><b>\n‣Stage 0 </b>\nBreast cancer has been diagnosed early. It started in the breast ducts or milk glands and has stayed there.<b>\n‣Stage 1 </b>\nStarting at this level, breast cancer is called invasive, meaning it has broken free to attack healthy tissue.<b>\n‣Stage 2</b>\nIn this stage the breast cancer has grown, spread or both.<b>\n‣Stage 3 </b>\nIn this stage breast cancer has not spread to bones or organs, but it’s considered advanced, and it’s harder to fight.<b>\n‣Stage 4</b> \nBreast cancer cells have spread far away from the breast and lymph nodes right around it. The most common sites for spreading are the bones, lungs, liver, and brain. This stage is described as “metastatic,” meaning it has spread beyond the region of the body where it was first found.<br />
    </string>

    <string name="o">Mammography (also called mastography) is the process of using low-energy X-rays (usually around 30 kVp) to examine the human breast for diagnosis and screening.The goal of mammography is the early detection of breast cancer.
        <b>\n• Right age to do mammography.</b> \nWe recommend mammogram screening to start no earlier than age 40. Women ages 40 to 44 should have the choice to start annual breast cancer screening with mammograms (x-rays of the breast) if they wish to do so. Women age 45 to 54 should get mammograms every year. Women 55 and older should switch to mammograms every 2 years, or can continue yearly screening</string>

</resources>